<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nate Laux</title>
    <link>https://www.natelaux.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nate Laux</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://www.natelaux.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Technical Writer who thrives on transforming complex developer concepts into clear, actionable documentation. With experience across blockchain, financial compliance, and investigations technology, I specialize in creating documentation that serves both technical and business needs.&#xA;My expertise includes crafting comprehensive API, SDK, and UI documentation in docs-as-code environments. I excel in information architecture and documentation automation, which paired with programming abilities for testing APIs, validating code examples, and building documentation tools, ensures documentation that truly serves customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>experience</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/experience/</guid>
      <description>A PDF of my résumé is available here. Alternatively, you can check out my LinkedIn profile.&#xA;Technical Writer, Chainalysis March 2021 - Present&#xA;At Chainalysis, I focus on delivering clear, accurate, and user-centric content for our API, SDK, and UI users in a docs-as-code environment. I collaborate cross-functionally with Product Managers, Engineering Managers, Product Design, Product Marketing, and Customer Support to ensure documentation meets both technical and business requirements. I own the documentation process from start to finish, from planning through delivery and maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>samples</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/samples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/samples/</guid>
      <description>OpenAPI Spec: I hand wrote an OAS definition. The preceding link showcases the final API reference. Each endpoint includes examples, accurate data types and nullability, and consistent, descriptive naming across requests, responses, and parameters.&#xA;Python Scripts: I write Python scripts with accompanying tutorials. This one calls an endpoint, applies a client-side filter that isn’t supported by query parameters, then calls another endpoint to action the data. The tutorial guides the user through the script’s functions with the goal of teaching how to use the endpoints in a live scenario.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
