<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nate Laux</title>
    <link>https://www.natelaux.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nate Laux</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.natelaux.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Based in Los Angeles, CA, I am a technical writer with a background in philosophy and a long history of transforming complex ideas into clear, accessible prose. Throughout my career, I have exhibited adept writing, thorough yet empathetic editing, strong research capabilities, along with outstanding collaboration and soft skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>experience</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/experience/</guid>
      <description>A PDF of my résumé is available here. Alternatively, you can check out my LinkedIn profile.
Relevant Work Chainalysis Technical Writer &amp;ndash; (March 2021 - Present)
Develop and maintain product documentation for a suite of API and non-API products See API documentation for products one, two, and three. Write and test Python scripts, create tutorials, and provide clear code examples for developers Utilize web development skills and tools for documentation enhancement, including custom CSS, HTML, webpage redirects, Google Analytics implementation, and automation using GitHub Actions Ensure documentation adheres to a coherent information architecture and follows organization’s style guide Collaborate effectively with Product, Engineering, Design, and Marketing teams to deliver accurate and comprehensive content Interview candidates and mentor other writers to strengthen the documentation team Naviga Technical Writer Contractor &amp;ndash; (November 2020 - March 2021)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>samples</title>
      <link>https://www.natelaux.com/samples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.natelaux.com/samples/</guid>
      <description>Developer Portal and REST API Reference Documentation
Product one Product two Product three Python Scraper and Corresponding Tutorial
I created a Python-based web scraper to extract winemaker profiles from the various online sources, translate the text to English, and store the gathered data in a CSV file. Alongside the script, I crafted an in-depth tutorial that guides readers through the process of building the web scraper, explaining the purpose and functionality of each code segment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
